Guide to the Entomological Society of America, Southeastern Branch, Records
Entomological Society of America, Southeastern Branch, Records
- Photographs, 1937-1997; 0.5 linear feet
  - Photographs: Robert T. Gast Award for Best Paper given by a Ph. D. Student, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Used for the Southeastern Branch Meeting Program, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Annual Meeting and Award Winners (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Annual Meeting and Award Winners (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)